

SUMMARY

7+ years experienced Technical Artist. Who worked on production on multi-disciplenary parts of game development process such as game development, shader creation, 3D game asset creation. Worked on multiple projects such as AR/VR game & applications, PC games & mobile games. Developed & published 2 mobile hit games in last 2 years.

SKILLS

- UNITY ENGINE
- UNREAL ENGINE
- C#
- HLSL/GLSL
- 3D/2D GAME ART
- HOUDINI

OĞULCAN KARAOĞLU

TECHNICAL ARTIST

CONTACT



∰ WEBSITE €



oulcankaraolu@gmail.com



+90 553 0470213

WORK EXPERIENCE



TECHNICAL ARTIST



FUNRIKA GAMES

2022 - Present



TECHNICAL ARTIST / GAME DEVELOPER



UNLIT GAMES

2020 - 2022



TECHNICAL ARTIST



MC GAME STUDIOS

2019-2020



TECHNICAL ARTIST



PANDORA AR & VR TECHNOLOGIES

2016 - 2019

EDUCATION

İTO Foundation Süleyman Taştekin Technical High School.

- High School Diploma, Information Technology
- Nov 2011 Jun 2015